

ABOUT ME

Technical Support Representative with one year of experience handling calls in the US and helping many applicants print out their clearance.

Many tools and software easily assist the customer's needs quickly; aside from that, I'm making a website and cleaning Databases data to avoid misspelt and null information inside the database using PostgreSQL and Oracle 11g.

LINKS

Microsoft Outlook: renstrio@outlook.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ware n-gador-18505b1b7/

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

FILIPINO

CEBUANO

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth Sept,15,1997

Nationality Filipino

Visa status N/A

Marital status Single

REFERENCES

AGNES MATSUO House Wife T: 639088178501

OLIVER ORILLO MFOJR Internet T: 639204379219

JESSICA LABUTAP Ass. Sec PNP Clearance T: 639997860445

WAREN GADOR I.T SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Blk 22, Molave St. Welfareville Compound Barangay Addition hills, Mandaluyong, 1550, Philippines

0

waren.gador15@gmail.com

0282788931

WORK EXPERIENCE

PNP POLICE CLEARANCE

Mandaluyong May 2018 - May 2019

ALORICA

Pasay City Feb 2021 - Aug 2022

Encoder

Encode all clients' personal information to submit and print out their clearance.

TSR - Technical Support

My job is to receive incoming calls about the client's problems over the phone and resolve the issues of the payment for their product.

EDUCATION

ASIAN INSTITUTE OF COMPUTER STUDIES

Quezon City 2018

Bachelor of Science

Learn how to know CCNA about Networking Topologies, C++, Oracle 11g Database Administrator Schemas, Html5, CSS, and Javascript.

Reformatting Computer Units.

ANDRES BONIFACIO INTEGRATED SCHOOL

Mandaluyong City 2015

Highschool (basic Curriculum)

1st Place in DAMATH. 1st Place in Poster Making Contest.

SKILLS

MS WORD	MS POWERPOINT
MS EXCEL	MS ACCESS
JAVA PROGRAMMING	HTML5

COURSE

ASIAN INSTITUE OF COMPUTER STUDIES Jun 2016 - Dec 2020 BS in Computer Science

HOBBIES

READING BOOKS, CODING, WATCHING MOVIES